{
    "subject": "resource/Operation_Gladio",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Stay-behind",
    "human_readable": "Operation Gladio is of the type Stay-behind.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8787841200828552,
            "question": "What type of operation is Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.728516161441803,
            "question": "Can you describe a 'Stay-behind' operation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6837164759635925,
            "question": "What are some lasting consequences of Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.624267041683197,
            "question": "What was the purpose of Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6199117302894592,
            "question": "Where was Operation Gladio primarily conducted?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.586487889289856,
            "question": "What were the intended outcomes of Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.516053318977356,
            "question": "When did Operation Gladio take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48541274666786194,
            "question": "Were there any controversies or criticisms surrounding Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4309902489185333,
            "question": "Who were the key players involved in Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3858632445335388,
            "question": "How did Operation Gladio impact international relations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Operation Gladio is of the type Stay-behind.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4531_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the key players involved in Operation Gladio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4531_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any controversies or criticisms surrounding Operation Gladio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4531_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Operation Gladio take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4531_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4531_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Operation Gladio is a clandestine NATO \"stay-behind\" operation, and also refer to it as a stay-behind organization. Therefore, the triple \"Operation Gladio is of the type Stay-behind\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Operation Gladio as a clandestine NATO \"stay-behind\" operation, which supports the statement that Operation Gladio is of the type Stay-behind."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}